{
	"regex1" : [
		{	
			"question" : ".",
			"name" : "regq1",
			"a1" : "Any character",
			"a2" : "Period",
			"a3" : "End of line",
			"a4" : "None of the above.",
			"answer" : 1
		},
		{
			"question" : "*",
			"name" : "regq2",
			"a1" : "All files",
			"a2" : "Any number of times",
			"a3" : "Focus on this",
			"a4" : "None of the above.",
			"answer" : 2
		}, 
		{
			"question" : "\\",
			"name" : "regq3",
			"a1" : "Escape next character",
			"a2" : "Website URL follows",
			"a3" : "Go down one directory",
			"a4" : "None of the above.",
			"answer" : 1
		}, 
		{
			"question" : "|",
			"name" : "regq4",
			"a1" : "End of line",
			"a2" : "Pipe this command",
			"a3" : "Or",
			"a4" : "None of the above.",
			"answer" : 3
		},
		{
			"question" : "(",
			"name" : "regq5",
			"a1" : "Start math operation",
			"a2" : "Start a capture group",
			"a3" : "Start a subcommand",
			"a4" : "None of the above.",
			"answer" : 2
		},
		{
			"question" : "[",
			"name" : "regq6",
			"a1" : "Start a character class",
			"a2" : "Start a math operation",
			"a3" : "Star command now",
			"a4" : "None of the above.",
			"answer" : 1
		},
		{
			"question" : "=",
			"name" : "regq7",
			"a1" : "Set variable to",
			"a2" : "Exactly equal to",
			"a3" : "distractor",
			"a4" : "None of the above.",
			"answer" : 1
		},
		{
			"question" : "?",
			"name" : "regq8",
			"a1" : "Question",
			"name" : "regq","a2" : 
			"Check validity",
			"a3" : "Zero or one quantifier",
			"a4" : "None of the above.",
			"answer" : 3
		},
		{
			"question" : "+",
			"name" : "regq9",
			"a1" : "Add",
			"a2" : "One or more quantifier",
			"a3" : "Combine two commands",
			"a4" : "None of the above.",
			"answer" : 1
		},
		{
			"question" : ")",
			"name" : "regq10",
			"a1" : "End capture group",
			"a2" : "End math operation",
			"a3" : "End command",
			"a4" : "None of the above.",
			"answer" : 1
		}
	],
	"regex2" : [
		{
		  "question" : ".$",
		  "name" : "reg2q1",
		  "a1" : "Would return \"f\" in \"abcdef\"",
		  "a2" : "Would return \"a\" in \"abcdef\"",
		  "a3" : "Would return \"c\" in \"abcdef\"",
		  "answer" : 1
		},{ 
		  "question" : "^a\\.",
		  "name" : "reg2q2",
		  "a1" : "Would return \"a\" in \"a first\" ",
		  "a2" : "Would return \"a first\"  in \"a first\"",
		  "a3" : "Would return nothing in \"a first\"",
		  "answer" : 3
		},{
		  "question" : "[a-z]",
		  "name" : "reg2q3",
		  "a1" : "Will match \"a\" but won't match \"z\"",
		  "a2" : "Won't match \"Z\" but will match \"!\"",
		  "a3" : "Won't match \"A\" but will match \"z\"",
		  "answer" : 3
		},{
		  "question" : "[a-z,A-Z]+ ?!?",
		  "name" : "reg2q4",
		  "a1" : "Will match \"Discovery\" and \"Discovery!\"",
		  "a2" : "Will match \"Discovery!\" and match \"Discovery!!\" ",
		  "a3" : "Will match \"Discovery!!\" and will match \"Discovery 2!\"",
		  "answer" : 1
		},{
		  "question" : "[0-9,:]+ (am|pm)",
		  "name" : "reg2q5",
		  "a1" : "Will match \"9:30 pm\" but not \"930pm\"",
		  "a2" : "Won't match \"930 am\" but will match \"9:30 am\" ",
		  "a3" : "Will match \"9:30 am\" and \"9:30 AM\"",
		  "answer" : 1
		},{
		  "question" : "[A-Z,a-z]+: ?.+",
		  "name" : "reg2q6",
		  "a1" : "Will match \"Introduction: Start here!\" but not match \"Introduction!: Start here.\"",
		  "a2" : "Will match \"Introduction: Start here!\" but not match \"Introduction:Start here!\"",
		  "a3" : "Will match \"Introduction: Start here!\" and will match \"Introduction::Start here!\"",
		  "answer" : 1
		},{
		  "question" : "[0-9,a-z,A-Z,!, ]+",
		  "name" : "reg2q7",
		  "a1" : "Will match \"It's his unicorn!\" but not match \"It's not his unicorn.\"",
		  "a2" : "Will match \"It is his Unicorn.\" and match \"It's his unicorn.\" ",
		  "a3" : "Won't match \"It's his unicorn.\" but will match  \"It is his Unicorn!\"",
		  "answer" : 3
		},{
		  "question" : "^a[^b-c]",
		  "name" : "reg2q8",
		  "a1" : "Will match  \"a new day\" and will match \"a bad day\" ",
		  "a2" : "Will match \"a new day\" but not match \"a bad day\"",
		  "a3" : "Will match \"a new day.\" and will match \"a new day\"",
		  "answer" : 2
		},{
		  "question" : "^a[^b-c]+[\\.]?",
		  "name" : "reg2q9",
		  "a1" : "Will match  \"a new day\" and will match \"a bad day\"",
		  "a2" : "Will match \"a new day\" but not match \"a bad day\"",
		  "a3" : "Will match \"a new day.\" but not match \"a new day\"",
		  "answer" : 2
		},{
		  "question" : "^[D,d].+[S,r]$",
		  "name" : "reg2q10",
		  "a1" : "Won't match \"Dragon slayer\" but will match \"Dragon Slayer\"",
		  "a2" : "Will match \"Dragon ride\" but won't match \"Dragon rider\"",
		  "a3" : "Will match \"Dragon Rider\" and will match \"Dragon slayer\"",
		  "answer" : 3
		}	
	]
}
